A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Scientific Staff Biographical Files FA260
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Scientific Staff Biographical Files
1904-1986
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
Rockefeller University
FA260
13.01 Cubic Feet 35 document cases
File Plan
Former Classification: I RG 450.1
Scope and Contents
This collection includes employment-related files for the scientific staff of the Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (later The Rockefeller University). The files appear to have originated as files on personnel kept by the Business Manager's Office.
Files typically include a copy of a formal grant application or an application for a staff appointment, letters of recommendation, correspondence with the head of the respective laboratory department, formal notices of appointments, renewal or resignation notices, and similar materials. For international applicants there is frequently correspondence with the Office of Immigration. Some files include clippings, obituaries, and photographs.
Dates given in the finding aid refer to the dates covered by the materials in the folder, not to the dates of appointment at the Rockefeller Institute. For information on the latter, the researcher may wish to consult "A History of the Rockefeller Institute, 1901-1953" by George W. Corner, published by the Rockefeller Institute Press, 1964.
Arrangement
The files are arranged in alphabetical order by last name.
Related Materials
For materials related to faculty, staff, and others associated with the Institute/University, the researcher may wish to consult FA259 Rockefeller University Campus Office Biographical Files. Some individuals may also have papers available. Consult Archivist for identification of pertinent materials and further assistance.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains material ranging from 1904 through the 1960s. Some files include clippings or obituary information published in the 1970s and 1980s.
Medical technology; Medicine, Preventive; Medical sciences; Medical research; Medical education; Science -- Study and teaching; Life sciences
- Abel, John J., 1914-1916, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Abernethy, Theodore J., 1932-1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Abraham, Leon J., 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Acs, George, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Adams, Mark H., 1938-1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Addis, Thomas, 1928-1930 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Alivisatos, Spyridion, 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Allen, Chester H., 1914-1917 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Allen, Frederick M., 1913-1930 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Allen, Raymond A., 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Alling, Eric L., 1925 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Alloway, J. Lionel, 1930, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Alpert, Louis, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Alvarez, Miguel, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Alving, Alf Sven, 1934, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Amano, Tsunehisa, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Amoss, Harold L., 1911-1934 (Box 1, Folder 19, Folder 18, Folder 21, Folder 20, Folder 23, Folder 22, Folder 17)
- Anderson, Harold C., 1946-1948, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Anderson, R.J., 1927-1931 (Box 1, Folder 26, Folder 25)
- Andrewes, Christopher H., 1923, 1931, 1949, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Ankel, Wulf Emmo, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Anslow, Major Ralph O., 1950 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Anson, Mortimer Louis, 1927-1943, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Anthony, Albert J., 1930-1947 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Archetti, Italo, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Armsby, H.P., 1920-1921 (Box 2, Folder 4, Folder 3)
- Armstrong, Alice H., 1927 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Astrom, Karl Erik, 1948-1950 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Atchley, William A., 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Auer, John, 1904-1927 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Auger, L. Carlton, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Austin, James Harold, 1919-1921 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Averell, Philip R., 1926, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Avery, Roy C., 1917, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Babers, Frank H., 1929-1952 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Bailey, John Leggett, 1953-1955 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Baird, Robert Desmond, 1935-1938 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Baker, Edgar E., Jr., 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Baker, James A., 1940-1947 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Baker, Lillian E., 1922-1942 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Ballentine, Robert, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Bancroft, Frank W., 1911-1915 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Bang, Frederick B., 1941-1947 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Barnes, Mario Garcia, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Barbarossa, Carlo, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Barber, Marshall A., 1919 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Barker, Bertha, 1906-1910 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Barker, W. Halsey, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Barkhuus, Arne, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Barrett, Morris K., 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Barrier, Charles W., 1919 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Barrnett, Russell J., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Barron, E.S. Guzman, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Barry, Guy Thomas, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Bartlett, Paul D., 1931, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Bartz, Quentin R., 1936 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Bass, Lawrence W., 1924-1944 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Battersby, Alan R., 1950 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Battistini, T.S., 1924-1925 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Battisto, Jack R., 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Baudisch, Oskar, 1923-1955 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Bauer, Karl, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Baxter, James H., 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Baylor, Martha B., 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Beach, Jerry R., 1929-1934 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Beard, Joseph W., 1932-1940 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Beattie, William Walter, 1925-1934 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Beatty, W.A., 1905-1907 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Beckman, W. Woods, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Beeson, Paul B., 1937 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Behrens, Otto Karl, 1937-1943 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Beiser, Sam, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Belcher, Donald, 1930-1945 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Bellin, Judith S., 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Bengtsson, Lars Philip, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Benjamin, Bernard, 1930-1931 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Bennett, Dorothea, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Bergel, Meny, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Beringer, Frederick M., 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Bernhard, William G., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Bernkopf, H., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Berry, George P., 1929-1949 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Berthelsen, Knud C., 1928 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Beutner, Reinhard, 1911-1953 (Box 3, Folder 26A, Folder 27, Folder 26)
- Beveridge, William I.B., 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Bibb, Louis B., 1928 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Bickford, James V., 1930 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Bigelow, Newell M., 1931-1933 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Bing, Richard, 1937-1952 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Binger, Carl, 1919-1976 (Box 4, Folder 6, Folder 5)
- Binkley, Francis, 1942-1952 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Biscoe, Jonathan, 1934, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Bjerrum, Jannik (Box 4, Folder 8A)
- Bjorkman, Sven E.F., 1946-1948 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Black, Lindsay M., 1936-1946 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Blake, John B., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Blankenhorn, David H., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Blankenhorn, Marion A., 1924-1925 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Blinks, Lawrence R., 1926-1933 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Bloch, Hubert C., 1947 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Blomstrand, Rolf L., 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Blondheim, Solomon H., 1948-1951 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Bogorad, Lawrence, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Böhme, Diethelm H., 1955-1958 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Böhmig, Richard, 1929-1932 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Boman, Hans G., 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Bomford, Richard R., 1938 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Bongiovanni, Alfred M., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Booth, V.H., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Boots, Ralph H., 1919-1935 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Borowitz, Irving J., 1958 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Boughton, Donald C., 1934-1937 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Bourdillon, Jacques, 1937, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Bouvier, Claude A.B., 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Bovarnick, Max, 1945-1946, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Boyd, Douglas, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Boyden, Stephen V., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Bradshaw, Benjamin C., 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Brakeley, Elizabeth, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Branch, Edmund Arnold, 1922-1926 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Brenner, Carl Max (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Brigham, M. Prince, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Bronner, Felix, 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Broome, J.D., 1957 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Brow, George Raymond, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Brown, Alfred S., 1932 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Brown, Goronwy O., 1920 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Brown, James Howard, 1917-1956 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Brown, Lenora Virginia (Lenora Brown Irwin), 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Brown, Thomas M., 1937 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Bruce, William F., 1932-1944 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Bruni, Carlo, 1956-1958 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Bruynoghe, R., 1927-1928 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Bryant, Gladys, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Buch-Anderson, Erik, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Bull, Carroll G., 1913-1933 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Bunting, Charles H., 1906-1914 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Burch, George E., 1939-1961, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Burgess, Laurie L., 1930-1931 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Butler, Alan M., 1926-1928 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Butler, J.A.V., 1939-1948 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Butterfield, E.E., 1907-1915 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Butterfield, E.E., 1907-1915 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Butterfield, E.E., 1907-1915 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Butterfield, E.E., 1907-1915 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Cain, Charles B., 1930-1931 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Caldwell, John, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Camber, Bernard, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Campbell, Berry, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Carpenter, Charles M., 1922 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Casals-Ariet, Jorge, 1937-1952, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Casals-Ariet, Jorge, 1937-1952, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Casals-Ariet, Jorge, 1937-1952, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Case, Francis H., 1925 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Casey, Albert E., 1927-1934 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Caspersson, T., 1939 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Cattaneo, Carlo, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Caulfield, James B., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Cazzullo, Carlo L., 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Chang, Hsiang-Tung, 1947-1958 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Cheng, Sze-chuh, 1955-1960 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Chesney, Alan M., 1914-1954 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Chester, Kenneth S., 1933-1949 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Chesterman, C.C., 1923-1927 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Chickering, Henry Thorndyke, 1913-1954 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Chinard, Francis P., 1945-1949 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Chou, Chi-yuan, 1939-1946 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Chow, Bacon F., 1932-1945 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Christie, Ronald V., 1926 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Christman, Clarence C., 1935-1938 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Chrobak, Louis, 1930-1931 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Clare, June V., 1956 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Clark, Earl Perry, 1917-1920 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Clark, Harry, 1919-1928 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Clark, Harry, 1919-1928 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Clark, Paul F., 1909-1914 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Clarke, Thomas W., 1907-1909 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Cluff, Leighton E., 1951-1953 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Clutton, R.F., 1938 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Coburn, Alvin F., 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Cochran, George W., 1941-1948 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Cohen, Seymour S., 1941-1942, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Cole, Roger D., 1956-1958 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Colin, Philip G., 1926-1927 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Collins, Arnold M., 1923-1925 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Compton, Jack, 1933-1936 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Condouris, George A., 1957 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- [not assigned] (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Conway, Dorothy M., 1957-1959 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Cooper, William C., Jr., 1925-1927 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Cope, Cuthbert L., 1931-1932 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Copeland, D. Eugene, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Corcoran, A. Curtis, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Corey, Robert B., 1928-1946 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Cori, Aida T., 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Cortese, Frank, 1930-1933 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Costa, Alvaro S., 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Costa, Luis F.M., 1959 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Cotzias, George C., 1945-1953 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Councilman, William T., 1913-1917 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Courtney, Angelia M., 1908-1919 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Coutinho, Elsimar, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Covell, Walter P., 1926-1927 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Cowperthwaite, Irving A., 1926, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Cox, Herald Rea, 1932-1936, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Crampton, Charles C., 1952-1954, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Crawford, J. Hamilton, 1922-1926, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Cretcher, Leonard H., 1916-1918 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Cross, Howard B., 1921-1922, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Cross, Howard B., 1921-1922, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Cross, Howard B., 1921-1922, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Cross, Howard B., 1921-1922, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Cross, Howard B., 1921-1922, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Cross, Howard B., 1921-1922, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Cullen, Ernest Glenn, 1913-1918 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Curnen, Edward C., Jr., 1939-1946 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Cutler, E.C., 1916 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Daddi, Giuseppe (Box 8, Folder 1)
- D'Abramo, Furio, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Dahl, Harry W., 1922-1923 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Dahl, Lewis Kitchener, 1947-1957, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Daly, Marie, 1948-1955 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Dam, Henrik, 1940, 1945-1946 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Damon, Edwin B., 1925, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Danchakoff, Vera, 1915-1916 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Das Gupta, S.N., 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Davenport, Fred M., 1946-1951 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Davidson, David, 1924 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Davies, H. Whitridge, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Davies, Howard G., 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Davies, John A.V., 1926, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Davis, Bernard D., 1945-1946 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Davis, John Staige, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Davis, Leverett, Jr., 1942-1946 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Dawson, James R., Jr., 1939, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Dawson, Martin H., 1928, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Dayhoff, Margaret O., 1948-1951 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- de Castro, Fernando, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Dehelly, George, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Deicher, Helmuth, 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- De Kock, Gilles, 1929-1930 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Delbrück, Axel, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- De Luca, Chester, 1957, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Denys, Pierre, 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Derick, Clifford L., 1924, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Dermby, Carl B., 1917 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- De Ropp, R.S., 1945 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Despopoulos, Agamemnon, 1948, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Desreux, Victor, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Deutsch, Harold F., 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Dexter, Smith O., Jr., 1938 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Dick, Macdonald, 1930-1933 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Dieke, Friedrich P.J., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Dieu, Hector A., 1947 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Di Ferrante, Nicola, 1953-1956 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Di Ferrante, Nicola, 1953-1956 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Dillon, Robert T., 1929-1937 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Diringer, Renata, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Di Somma, August A., 1936 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Dmochowski, Anthony, 1930-1931 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Doan, Charles A., 1925-1930 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Dobriner, Konrad, 1936-1939, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Dole, Malcolm, 1928-1930, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Dougherty, Katharine (White), 1919-1920, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Dow, Robert Stone, 1938, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Downie, Allan Watt, 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Downs, Cora M., 1939 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Drury, Douglas R., 1922, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Dublin, Thomas D., 1937, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Dubuisson, Marcel, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Duffy, Carl E., 1944 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Dukes, Charles D., 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Dumbell, Keith R., 1951-1953 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Duran-Reynals, Francisco, 1926-1958 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Duran-Reynals, Francisco, 1926-1958 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Duval, Charles, 1904-1913 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Duval, Charles, 1904-1913 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Duval, Charles, 1904-1913 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Ebashi, Setsuro, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Ebeling, Albert H., 1915-1929, 1939-1946, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Ebeling, Albert H., 1915-1929, 1939-1946, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Eberson, Frederick, 1915-1918 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Ecker, Paul G., 1947 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Eder, Howard, 1945-1952 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Edman, Pehr, 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Edwards, Joshua L., 1952-1955 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Ehrich, Wilhelm E., 1926-1932, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Ehrich, Wilhelm E., 1926-1932, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Eisenmenger, William J., 1947-1954 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Elderfield, Robert C., 1930-1951 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Eldridge, Lewis A., Jr., 1926 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Ellis, Arthur W.M., 1911-1914 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- du Noüy, Pierre Lecomte (Box 9A, Folder 1)
- du Noüy, Pierre Lecomte (Box 9A, Folder 2)
- du Noüy, Pierre Lecomte (Box 9A, Folder 3)
- Elman, Robert, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Elrod, R. Perry, 1941-1951 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Elsbach, Peter, 1955-1959 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Emerson, Kendall, Jr., 1939-1946 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Enger, Per S., 1956-1958 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- England, Albert C., Jr., 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Ensinck, John W., 1957-1960 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Erdmann, Rhoda, 1912-1918, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Erdmann, Rhoda, 1912-1918, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Erdmann, Rhoda, 1912-1918, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Erf, Lowell, 1937-1939 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Ernster, Lars, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Faber, Harold K., 1915, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Faerber, Ernest E., 1941 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Farr, Lee, 1934-1954 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Fasoli, Angelo, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Faulkner, James Morison, 1925-1926 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Favilli, G., 1930 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Favour, Cutting B., 1946-1950 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Fawcett, Don W., 1951-1953 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Febvre, Henri L., 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Feinstein, Alvan R., 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Felton, Lloyd D., 1920-1924, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Feng, Teh-pei, 1941, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Fenn, Wallace O., 1921-1924, 1943-1945 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Fenn, Wallace O., 1921-1924, 1943-1945 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Fenner, Frank J., 1948-1949, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Ferguson, Malcolm, 1937-1947 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Fernandez, Antonio Gallego, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Fiala, Silvio, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 1A)
- Finkle, Philip, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Firket, Henri, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Fischer, Albert, 1920-1931 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Fisher, Gertrude G., 1916-1917 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Fite, George L., 1932-1935 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Fitz, Reginald, 1915, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- FitzGerald, Mabel, 1907-1910 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Fleck, Elmer E., 1928-1936 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Florence, Laura, 1918-1925, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Florman, Alfred L., 1946 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Folch-Pi, Jordi (Jorge), 1935-1947, 1977, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Folch-Pi, Jordi (Jorge), 1935-1947, 1977, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Folch-Pi, Jordi (Jorge), 1935-1947, 1977, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Forkner, Claud E., 1926-1927, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Forsbeck, Filip, 1929-1931 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Forsham, Peter, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Forssman, (Claes) Olof, 1952-1954 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Foster, Albert D., Jr., 1943-1945 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Fraenkel-Conrat, Heinz (Box 11, Folder 19A)
- Francis, Thomas, Jr., 1921-1954 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Francis, William L., 1933-1934 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Frankel, Florence H., 1916-1917 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Franklin, Edward C., 1954-1958, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Franhs, M. B., 1944 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Frenster, John H., 1958, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Friedewald, William F., 1938, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Friedheim, Ernst, 1930-1931, 1939, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Frishkopf, Lawrence S., 1957-1959 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Fruton, Joseph S., 1934-1954 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Furth, Jacob, 1926-1947, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Futcher, Palmer H., 1938-1942 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- [not assigned] (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Garcia-Bilbao, D. José L., 1956-1959 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Garnjobst, Laura F., 1957-1977 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Gasic, Gabriel, 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Gaupp, R., 1938 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Gaw, Harry Zanyin, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Gay, Frederick P., 1913-1916 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Geiger, J. Theodore, 1931, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Gelarie, Arnold J., 1913-1934 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Gelarie, Arnold J., 1913-1943 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Gelfand, Martin, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Genest, Jacques, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Gentzkow, C. J., 1936 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Gerominus, Lippman H., 1949-1952 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Giges, Burton, 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Gilchrist, A. Rae, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Gilder, Helena, 1941-1946 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Gilding, Henry P., 1927-1933 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Ginsberg, Harold S., 1946-1951 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Githens, Thomas S., 1910-1919 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Glaser, Rudolf William, 1916-1948, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Glaser, Rudolf William, 1916-1948, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Glaser, Rudolf William, 1916-1948, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Glaser, Rudolf William, 1916-1948, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Glasstone, Violette, 1939-1942 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Glauert, Audrey, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Glenn, E. Myles, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Goddard, David R., 1933-1935 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Goldthwaite, N.E., 1906-1909 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Golumbic, Calvin, 1942-1945 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Good, Robert A., 1949-1957 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Goodner, Kenneth, 1930-1946 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Gosting, Louis J., 1948 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Goto, Kingo, 1917-1918 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Goto, Masayosi, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Gould, Robert G., Jr., 1936-1942 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Grace, Thomas D.C., 1957-1959 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Graham, George L., 1933-1947 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Grant, Joseph H.B., 1923 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Gratia, André, 1920, 1937-1939 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Gratia, André, 1920, 1937-1939 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Grave, Thomas B., 1927-1929 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Gray, David, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Graybill, Harry W., 1915-1927 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Green, Robert H., 1940-1953 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Greene, Harry S.N., 1930-1953 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Greenspan, Joseph, 1942-1943 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Grégoire, Charles, 1946-1947 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Greif, Roger L., 1946-1953 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Grimsson, Halldor, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Gros, François, 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Gross, Erhard, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Gross, Samson R., 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Grossfeld, Henry, 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Grundfest, Harry, 1935, 1945-1953 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Guerreiro, Milton G., 1947 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Gundlach, (Hans) Gerd, 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Gustafson, Jryggve Ulf, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Gustus, Edwin L., 1925-1933 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Haagen, Eugen, 1927-1929, 1947, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Haas, Hermann J., 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Haelterman, Edward O., 1958 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Haessler, Ferdinand H., 1919 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Hagan, William A., 1921, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Hagiwara, Susumu, 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Hajossi-Kerek, Gyorgyi, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Haller, Herbert L., 1923, 1929, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Hamilton, Paul B., 1940-1948 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Hampil, B., 1938 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Hance, Robert T., 1924-1927 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Hanke, Martin E., 1930 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Hannon, Robert R., 1928 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Hanson, E. Jean, 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Hardy, Paul Harold, Jr., 1946-1948 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Harfenist, Elizabeth J. (Underhill), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Harford, Carl G., 1936-1937 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Harnes, Alvin R., 1927, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Harris, Albert H., 1936 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Harris, Earl S., 1925-1930 (Box 13, Folder 40)